{
    "id": "6a505387376e43078c843e63e3bb186d",
    "title": "Have And Do Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. you known him for long?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01b2715eb24c49d68cea9308639a8c2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... she speak English?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do",
                "Has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aedc24a9529c44e6befee9208c133642"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where could they ……………….. gone?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff6b3d8d96014bc1863e12370c2b940b"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he be able to do this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c9ddbf3ad8647c087961909bb818c8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you manage to find him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ab45b60447c45008b447d5a83dd06e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. she say anything?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "584108cd69a2495a86a66aa4266ccd34"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went there but I ………………. not see anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "366ede39f2af49eca26c913e5d85b264"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. not know what he is doing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "has",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "566f96908b2e49d1877c3fe12a969eac"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. never been to Australia.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3eab7c788f08400d949be09242bfa72b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… not get along with her neighbors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "decc08d00a124db69d5ec888ac67323f"
        }
    ]
}